YYeTs人人影视字幕组出品
更多原创字幕翻译 请登陆www.YYeTs.com
■
时间轴：godwuwen
后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
■
翻译： Vero  非燕  独醉  猫中之王
后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
■
校对： YY    后期：孤帆字幕总监： YY
老爸老妈浪漫史
第八季  第二集
孩子们  2012年的夏天堪称爱之夏
Kids, the summer of 2012 was the Summer of Love.
巴尼和昆茵
Barney and Quinn,
我和维多利亚
me and Victoria,
罗宾和尼克
Robin and Nick,
莉莉  马修和小马文
Lily, Marshall and Marvin.
每个人都沉浸在幸福中
Everyone was happy as can be.
这就意味没什么好故事可以讲
Which means there are absolutely no good stories.
我们直接跳到
Let's skip ahead...
2012年10月
...to October 2012,
正式分离的月份  也就是我们熟知的
the official kick-off of what came to be known as
分手之秋
the Autumn of Breakups.
三天前
这一切始于巴尼
It all started when Barney got
从同事那里得到一条友好的建议
a little friendly advice from a coworker.
定份婚前协议
Get a prenup,
不然我就在她之前阉了你
or I'll neuter you before she ever has a chance!
首先  你要是吃了洋葱圈
First of all, if you have an onion bagel,
就不要再吃大葱奶油干酪了
you don't need scallion cream cheese.
再说  昆茵是个好女孩
Secondly, Quinn is a great girl.
我信任她
I trust her.
达琳当初也是个好女孩
Oh, Darlene was a great girl.
我也信任过她
I trusted her.
可后来她夺走了一切
And then she took everything!
我的房子  我的车
My house, my car...
我的爱犬小拖船
my dog Tugboat.
我甚至在孩子方面也输了
I even lost out with the kids.
全部监护权
Full custody!
我得到了孩子的全部监护权
I got full custody of those kids!
你的孩子太可怕了
Your kids are horrible.
简直是混世魔王
The worst.
巴尼  我看着达琳
Barney, I watched as Darlene
把我生活中美好的东西一一切除
cut everything good out of my life
就像一个神经错乱的外科医生在切除器官
like a deranged surgeon hacking out organs,
我说这话不是在比喻
and that's not a metaphor.
她真的拿走了我的一颗肾
She got one of my kidneys.
这是她的来电铃声
That's her ringtone.
我已经一无所有了  达琳
I have nothing left to give you, Darlene!
你们不会相信巴尼今天做了什么
You won't believe what Barney did today.
你们不会相信昆茵今天做了什么
You won't believe what Quinn did today.
可以去吃午饭了吗
Hey, you ready for lunch?
她来了
Hey, there she is.
未来的巴尼・斯丁森太太
The future Mrs. Barney Stinson.
你最好珍惜一下签名还能
You better enjoy signing your name "Quinn Garvey"
签"昆茵・加维"的最后时光
while you still can, right?
不如这就签上
Like, I don't know...
这里  这里  这里首字母大写
here, here, here, initial here...
这是什么
What is this?
这是我们的婚前协议
Oh, this is our prenup.
黑笔或蓝笔  完全由你做主
Black or blue? Totally up to you.
我能先看看吗
Um, can I read it first?
难以置信
Can you believe that?
他想让我签婚前协议
He wants me to sign a prenup!
难以置信
Can you believe that?
她还想先看看
She wants to read it first!
你就直接签吧
Just go ahead and sign.
都是些标准化条款
It's all pretty standard.
离婚后
"In the event of divorce,
斯丁森先生可获准每周探视一次
"Mr. Stinson is granted weekly visitation rights
安娜  萨拉和茉莉
to Ann, Sarah and Molly."
你还给我们将来的孩子取了名吗
You named our future kids?
这还蛮贴心的
That's actually pretty sweet.
那些是斯丁森先生为您的三点区域取的名
Those are Mr. Stinson's names for your lady parts.
孩子们要跟爸比维持良好的关系
It's important for the girls to maintain a relationship
这点很重要哦
with their daddy.
你给她的三点区取了名吗
You named her lady parts?
大家都这么做
Everyone does that.
那么  莉莉的是
So... Lily?
噼啪  咔嚓  砰
Snap, Crackle, Pop.
-有默契  -等等
- Solid. - Wait.
这种婚前协议合乎常理吗
Is this prenup in any way legit?
我是说  目前为止  这听起来
I mean, so far, it sounds a lot like
就像是你写在酒吧纸巾上的一夜情协议
that bar napkin document you make one-night stands sign,
好保证事后不会缠着你
promising not to get clingy.
那是滚床单前协议  专利申请中
The Pre-Shtup, patent pending.
天啊  我得多想点好点子
God, I gotta come up with a lot of good stuff!
总之  我意识到
Anyway, I realize
这些并不只是离婚协议  所以我问...
these aren't just terms for divorce, so I ask...
这些是我要在婚后如何表现的规矩吗
Are these rules for how I have to behave in our marriage?
规矩
Rules?
是建议
Suggestions.
那些富人和名人常常把这些
Rich people and celebrities put stuff like this
写进他们的婚前协议里
in their prenups all the time.
而那些婚姻都得以持久
And those are the marriages that last.
我每长一磅就要付你两千美元
I have to pay $2,000 every time I gain a pound?
不是每长一磅就算
Not every time.
只有每周过磅的时候才算
Just if it shows up at the weekly weigh-in.
你不能这么做
See, you can't do that.
加维小姐每年必须发明
"Miss Garvey must invent 12 new
12个新的性爱姿势
sexual positions per year,
其中至少10个姿势
"At least ten of which
是全部或大部分由她主动
involve her doing all or most of the work."
你绝对不能这么做
You definitely can't do that.
加维小姐必须每五年做一次隆乳
"Miss Garvey's breasts must be enhanced every five years
或五万次抓胸  先后次序随意
or 50,000 honka-honkas, whichever comes first."
-这其实不错  -这条我同意
- That's actually not bad. - I'll allow it.
这简直太变态了
That's repulsive.
再说  男人怎么会觉得
And, sidebar: why do men think
女人喜欢被抓胸呢
women like to be honka-honka'd?
什么女人会喜欢自己的胸被挤得像牛角
What woman wants her breasts squeezed like a seal horn?
对啊  就是
Um... totally.
莉莉就很爱被抓胸
Lily like-a-like-a the honka-honka.
脖子以下的毛发必须每周脱一次
"All hair below the neck must be removed weekly."
每周过磅的时候  你会因为少了毛发的重量
Hey, you're gonna be thanking me for that hair loss
而感谢我的
during the weigh-in.
加维的父母可以在我们家
"Miss Garvey's parents may stay at our place
想待多久待多久
as long as they like."
至少这条不错
Well, at least that one's nice.
前提是他们被火化装进骨灰盒
Provided they each arrive in an urn.
妻子二号到八号  每周要有两位做家里的杂务
"Wives two through eight will make a weekly chore wheel.
抱歉  我从一个沙特阿拉伯的苏丹人
I'm sorry, I borrowed a few sections
制定的婚前协议里借鉴了几条
from a prenup I did for a Saudi Arabian sultan.
我会把其他一夫多妻的条款划掉
I'll cross out the extra wives stuff.
-除非...  -划掉
- Unless... - Cross it out.
天啊  巴尼到底觉得
My God! What the hell does Barney think
婚姻意味着什么啊
marriage is going to be like, anyway?
健康现代的婚姻是建立在
Just a healthy, modern-day marriage,
两个平等的人相互尊重的基础上
based on mutual respect between two equals.
主人  准备好享受您的叫醒大腿舞了吗
Ready for your wake-up lap dance, Master?
你是不是忘了什么
Aren't you forgetting something?
天啊  现在早上九点了
Oh, my God, it's 9:00 a.M.
依法须执行的晨间枕头大战时间
Legally mandated morning pillow fight time!
史上最棒老公
Best husband ever.
史上最棒...
Best husband e...
抱歉抱歉  我们划掉妻子二号到八号
Sorry, sorry, we crossed out the wives
只保留您这个大老婆  除非...
two through eight stuff. Unless...
-没门  -好吧
- Nope. - Okay.
别担心  我划掉了
Don't worry. I crossed it out.
其实我没划掉
I didn't really cross it out.
我听到了
I can hear you.
我会划掉的
I'll cross it out.
我才不会真划掉
I didn't really cross it out.
伙计们  怎么了
Hey, guys, what's up?
昆茵生气了
Oh, Quinn's pissed
巴尼想让她签一份疯狂的婚前协议
because Barney wants her to sign a crazy prenup.
真有那么疯狂吗
But is it really crazy?
-对  -虽然我刚到  但我猜也是
- Yes. - Well, I'm new to this but guessing yes. Yes.
听着  那我有没有...
Okay, look. Did I go...
做出像一粒沙  一根仙女的睫毛
a speck of sand, a fairy eyelash,
一声独角兽的耳语那么过分的要求呢
a unicorn whisper too far?
或许吧
Perhaps.
但是难道你们就敢说
But can you tell me there's nothing
在你们的感情中  没有一点需要改变的地方吗
in any of your relationships you'd want to change?
没有想摒弃的行为吗
No behavior you'd want to outlaw?
没有想重新协商的地位吗
No terms you'd want to renegotiate?
想清楚再看着我的眼睛  说我疯了
Look me in the eye and tell me I'm crazy.
你疯了
You're crazy.
可当晚  有意思的事发生了
But a funny thing happened that night.
我没说他说是对的  可...
Look, I'm not saying he's right, but
巴尼的话的确有点道理
Barney does have a little bit of a point.
在这一点上  他可能说得道理
But on this one, he may have a point.
我是说
I mean, look...
重新协商感情中两人地位的想法
the idea of renegotiating the terms of the relationship,
是正确的
that's valid.
才不是
No.
你没有任何我想改变的地方
There isn't anything about you that I'd want to change.
或许是有那么一两个地方
Well, okay, maybe a couple of things.
比如什么
Like what?
就这样
And just like that...
这四对情侣中  有一对会在第二天分手
one of these four couples would break up the very next day.
当然不是莉莉和马修
Okay, it wasn't Lily and Marshall.
这三对中  有一对会在第二天分手
One of these three couples would break up
怎么了
What happened?
昨晚尼克一直在说
So last night Nick was all like,
巴尼在"协商关系"这点上说得有道理
"Barney has a point "About renegotiating the terms
然后说了一堆有的没的废话
of the blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah."
对啊  马修也这样
Yeah, and Marshall was all like,
说什么"我想干嘛干嘛"
"Uh, I want to blah, of the blah,
废话一堆
uh, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah."
如果我闭上眼睛  仿佛能感觉到他们的存在
If I shut my eyes it's like they're here.
他们在借巴尼的婚前协议
They're just using Barney's prenup
来抱怨我们的不是
as a way to complain about us.
我只是说  你禁止了一些
I'm just saying, you've forbidden certain things
我可能还会想去做的事
that I might like to revisit.
马修  你不许再跟一群疯子
Marshall, you're not going on a Sasquatch hunt
去俄勒冈州追寻大脚野人了
in Oregon with a bunch of loonies.
疯子
Loonies?
那些勇敢的大胡子男女都是神秘生物学家
Those brave, bearded men and women are crypto-zoologists,
你起码该对他们的职称有所尊重
and they deserve the respect that title commands.
但那不是我想说的重点
But that's not what I was thinking of.
我想说的是  你太宝贝孩子了
You're too precious with the baby.
好吧  我们第一次带马文回家
Okay, when we first came home with Marvin,
发生了点不愉快
there was a bad moment.
欢迎回家  孩子
Welcome home, buddy.
真有抛那么高吗
Was it really that high?
我不知道  我当时荷尔蒙作祟
I don't know. I was hormonal.
突然间  这个压抑已久
And suddenly, this primal,
充满保护欲的母亲的声音嚷了出来
protective mother voice came out of me.
事实上  是两个声音
Actually, it was two voices.
我严重觉得有一个是我阴道的声音
I seriously think one was coming from my vagina.
以后再也别这样了
Never do that again!
有什么大不了的
What is the big deal?
我爸和我哥哥以前总把我扔来扔去的
My brothers and my dad used to roughhouse with me all the time.
欢迎回家  马修
Welcome home, Marshall.
孩子们
Hi. Boys...
接好
go long.
住手  不许在屋里玩
Stop! Not in the house.
灯就是被你这么打碎的
That's how lamps break.
想玩宝宝  到外面去
Now go pass that baby around outside.
哎呀  没接住
Oh, fumble!
我还不是茁壮成长了吗
And I turned out perfectly fine.
马修  今天早上你还以为
Marshall, this morning you thought
你的烤面包是鬼做的呢
a ghost made your toast.
我没把面包放进去
I didn't put the bread in.
你也没把面包放进去
You didn't put the bread in.
我要跟我的儿子玩
You know what? I will play with my son
我自有分寸  还有就是
however I see fit. And you know what else?
今晚你得"自娱自乐"了
You can honka-honka yourself tonight.
巴尼的婚前协议也毁了我的夜晚
Barney's prenup ruined my night, too.
我哪种行为你不喜欢了
Okay, uh, what behavior of mine don't you like?
我是说看电视那个
I'm talking about the TV thing.
我们因为看电视吵架
Okay, the TV thing is an argument
是从三周前就开始了
from, like, three weeks ago.
抱歉
Oh, I'm sorry.
没想到要42英寸
Didn't realize it takes 42 inches
才能让你满足
to keep you satisfied.
电视正好开着
The TV happened to be on.
我正好瞥到一眼
I happened to glance at it.
-那样会很怪吗  -不会啊
- Does that make me so weird? - No.
-一点也不  -谢谢
- Not at all. - Thank you.
我可能是有点怪
I may be a little weird.
真舒服
Oh, yeah.
做爱时  我看着自己播新闻的样子
I get... turned on watching myself
变得无比性奋
do the news during sex.
对  是有点奇怪
Yeah, that's a little weird.
听着  看着电视上的自己
Look, seeing myself on TV makes me
让我觉得自信又性感
feel confident and sexy.
没什么好丢人的  是吧  姐妹们
And that is nothing to be ashamed of, right, sisters?
-这事别再提了  -永远别提
- Never speak of this. - Ever.
好  那是当然
Yeah, of course. Yeah.
其实还有
There's more.
等等
Wait.
你在直播早上七点新闻的时候
So when you're doing the news live at 7:00,
对晚上看十一点重播的自己抛媚眼
you wink to future you watching the rebroadcast at 11:00?
可能吧
Maybe.
-这事别再提了  -永远别提
- Never speak of this.- Ever
你们不会相信
You won't believe
泰德昨晚干了什么好事
what Ted did last night.
你说你很乐意帮他
You said you were happy to help him out.
现在我改主意了
Well, now I'm changing my mind.
抱歉打扰了  室友
Sorry to interrupt, roomie,
我想做香肠
but I am trying to make sausage.
你家猪肠子放在哪里
Where do you keep your pig intestines?
你的前未婚夫在泰德家干嘛
What's your ex-fiance doing at Ted's?
克劳斯几周前来找我
Klaus came to me a few weeks ago.
我们分手后
Since we broke up,
他失业了  又被房东赶了出来
he lost his job, he got evicted.
他太惨了
He's miserable.
不好意思
I'm so sorry.
如果你能让我在你家厨房水槽
If I could just take a quick whore's bath
洗洗腋下和胯下  然后我立马走人
in your kitchen sink, then I will skedaddle.
克劳斯  真希望我能帮你做点什么
Oh, Klaus, I wish that there was something I could do to help.
你能  小姑娘
There is, little lady.
我这儿有客房
I've got a guest room.
你在回到正轨前  就住在这里好了
You'll stay here till you're back on your feet.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
这是你的公寓
This is your apartment.
把这里当作是我们的公寓吧
Think of this as our apartment.
扮英雄的泰德
Hero Ted.
他好喜欢这样
He loves that move.
是呀  过不了五分钟  英雄就会后悔
Yeah, for about five minutes, then he gets hero's remorse.
多谢你了  室友
Danke schon, roomie.
我去拿行李
I will go get my things.
这真是太好了太好了
Das is super-duper-duper.
我的雪貂一定开心死了
My ferrets will be so happy.
它们已经在机场储物柜住了几星期了
They have been living in an airport locker for weeks.
爸爸来了  孩子们
Here comes papa, children.
我承认
I'll admit,
的确有些时候蛮尴尬的
there have been a few awkward moments.
你们肯定会喜欢这个的
You are going to love this.
这是德国最受欢迎的情景喜剧
This is the popular German situational-comedy,
《陌生的同胞》
Strange Compatriots.
开始咯
Here we come.
我跟你讲讲这个节目哈
Ooh. Here's the thing about this show, okay?
其中有一个人非常好
One of them is very neat
另一个人  则是非常非常的好
und the other one is very, very neat.
弗理兹  过来
Oh, Fritz, kommen sie hier.
弗理兹
Ah, Fritz...
是时候把克劳斯踹走了
It's time to give Klaus "Das boot."
克劳斯
Klaus?
等等  隔着墙你都能听到我们讲话吗
Wait, can-can you hear us through the wall?
是的  可以听到
Yes, I can hear you.
什么都听得到哦
I hear everything.
受不了了
That's it.
克劳斯  进来
Klaus, get in here!
我的天
For God's sake.
我要你离开我的公寓
I want you out of my apartment.
你  那些雪貂  还有五只刚出生的
You, those ferrets and all five newborns.
是六只  继续计数中
Six and counting.
妈妈还在生呢
Mama is still going.
它那里就像小丑车一样
It is like a clown car.
一个接一个地出来
突然之间  没有"我们的"公寓这一说了
Suddenly, it wasn't our apartment anymore.
我没有发言权了
I had no say in the matter.
这些家伙太不像话了
These guys are unbelievable.
我这就回家
You know what, I am gonna go home
自己一个人"看"新闻
and watch the news all by myself.
等等
Wait.
我有个主意
I have an idea.
知道吗
You know what?
我同意签署婚前协议
I'm on board with the whole prenup thing.
太好了
That's great.
婚前协议也是保护你啊  小甜心
It's here to protect you, too, sweetie...
以防你变得对我不具吸引力
from becoming unappealing to me.
事实上  我找人帮了点忙
Actually, I made my own prenup
拟定了自己的婚前协议
with a little help.
女士们
Ladies?
直接签字吧  全是标准的法律条款
Go ahead and sign. It's all pretty standard.
现在可能不太合适问这个
This might not be the best time to ask--
我现在算是重回情场了
I'm sort of getting back in the game.
那个抱孩子的红发妞
The redhead with the baby,
有主了吗
what's her situation?
离婚后  加维小姐将获得
"In the event of divorce, Miss Garvey shall get
斯丁森先生西服的全部监护权
full custody of Mr. Stinson's suits"?
为什么
Why?
-你怎么处理它们  -置之不理
- What would you do with them? - Nothing.
我就是坐着看它们慢慢过时
I'd just sit around and watch them go out of style.
这也太变态了吧
That is just sick.
继续看吧
Keep reading.
斯丁森先生可以参加
"Mr. Stinson is allowed to attend
花花公子女郎宿舍的任何活动
any function at the Playboy Mansion."
至少这条不错
Well, at least that's nice.
前提是他被火化装进骨灰瓮
"Provided he arrives in an urn."
先生们  来得正好
Gentlemen, just in time.
你们这些贱人来干嘛
What are you bitches doing here?
-莉莉  -他在睡觉
- Lily. - Oh, he's napping.
只有这时候我才能发泄两句
It's the only time I get to go blue.
巴尼发短信说你们集体来找他茬
Barney texted us that you guys were ganging up on him.
所以我们只是来确保
So we're just here to ensure
他不会签什么会让他后悔的东西
he doesn't sign anything he'll regret.
不好意思  这里只有我才是律师
I'm sorry, I don't think anyone here other than me is a lawyer.
一名高薪成功的律师
A well-paid, successful lawyer.
我也是律师
I-I'm a lawyer.
事实上  我们曾共事过几年
Actually, we worked together for years.
闪一边儿去  大高个  是我先瞧见她的
Back off, stretch, I saw her first.
等等
Hang on a second.
只要斯丁森先生不能"随鸡变硬"
"A half million dollar fine any time Mr. Stinson can't
就要处以50万美元的罚款
'rise to the occasion,'
提示  悲惨的下垂口哨声
cue sad slide whistle sounds"?
这个电击圈是怎么回事
Hey, what's this about a shock collar?
那个啊  我们来解释
Ah, yes, we'll explain.
加维小姐会有很多的迷人的朋友来做客
Miss Garvey has many attractive friends who will come to visit.
来点我做的山羊奶酪酥吗  小姐
May I offer you some goat cheese puff pastries I made, mistress?
只要你默默端上来就行
As long as you can do it quietly.
慢着  我糊涂了
Wait, I'm confused.
如果不是套在我脖子上
If it's not around my neck,
那这个电击圈套在哪里啊
then where's the shock collar?
我的娘哟
Oh, God.
我的亲娘哟
其实说电击环更准确些
It's more of a shock ring, really.
她的主意
Her idea.
原来是美貌与智慧并存啊
Little missy is packing a brain, too.
好吧
Okay, you know what?
既然我们都来了
Since we're all pitching in,
我能建议加项条款吗
may I suggest a provision?
你们生了儿子以后  斯丁森先生有权以
In the event that you have a son, Mr. Stinson is free
他认为适当的方式和儿子玩耍
to play with his child however he sees fit.
再加一条禁止你未来的老公
How about forbidding your future husband
用球棒把孩子打进婴儿床如何
from spiking his child into his crib?
再加一条避免你被她用来
How about a clause protecting you from having to engage
和常规电视节目玩"三人行"的条款如何
in a three-way with her and whatever's on basic cable?
是吗  那要不要禁止
Oh, yeah? How about forbidding...
我想不出来
I got nothing.
再加一条禁止光屁股前德国佬未婚夫
How about a provision barring any nudist German ex-fiance
在我的沙发上磨蹭他的"香肠"如何
from slapping his strudel up and down your sofa?
再加上逞能装英雄
How about pretending to be a hero,
结果被雪貂咬破皮就怂成软蛋了如何
but then caving the moment a ferret bite breaks the skin?
是咬破了我的眼皮
The skin of my eyelid.
那是雪貂亲吻的方式
That's how they kiss.
你是认真的吗
Are you serious?
够了  够了
Enough! Enough!
你们都拥有深爱自己的人
You all have someone who loves you,
却要亲手毁掉这一切  为了什么啊
and you're screwing it up, and over what?
就为了比谁权力大吗
Who has the most power?
这不是真爱
That's not love.
真爱是足够信任对方
Love is trusting someone enough
敢于说出让自己困扰的事情
to tell them what's really bothering you.
所以我们就要这么做
So that's what we're gonna do.
从你开始
You, start.
当你为了马文惊慌失措时
When you got scared about Marvin,
感觉好像你在暗示
it felt like you were saying that
我不是像你这样称职的父母
I'm not as good a parent as you.
你是个很棒的妈妈
You're an amazing mom,
我希望能和你一样
and I want to live up to that.
我可能会对别人缺乏信任
Well, I probably have trust issues
因为小时候爸爸总不在我身边
because my dad wasn't there for me.
但我知道你会永远稳稳地接住马文
But I know that you'll always be there to catch Marvin.
接下来轮到你
You, next.
跟克劳斯住在一起
Having Klaus back in our lives
让我害怕我们永远摆脱不了过去
made me scared we're never gonna escape the past.
我之所以想帮克劳斯
I only wanted to help Klaus
是因为我们的幸福  让我觉得有愧于他
because I feel guilty about how happy I am with you.
到你们了
Next.
我觉得你非常性感
I find you so sexy,
而发现你对我没有同样的感觉  我很受伤
it just hurt that you don't feel the same about me.
我做爱时  会被播新闻的自己挑起"性"致
I get turned on watching myself do the news during sex.
我可以接受
Well, that's cool.
看看  不需要任何法律文件
Look at that, no legal documents needed.
只需坦诚相对  愿意改变
Just honesty and vulnerability.
这就是爱
That's love.
曾经我也深爱过某人
You see, I once loved someone,
可惜我说得不够多
only I didn't say it enough.
现在我希望我每天都大声地说出来
Now I wish I could say it every day.
管它疯不疯狂
Hell, i don't care if it's crazy,
我要弥补回来
I-I'm doing it.
达琳吗
Hello, Darlene?
让小拖船听电话
Put Tugboat on the line.
老伙计
Hey, buddy.
是我啊
Hey, it's the man.
在那一刻
And for a moment,
世界回到了正轨
all felt right with the world.
但当天夜里
But that very night,
分手之秋出现了第一对受害者
the Autumn of Breakups would claim its first victims.
祝您今晚平安  愉快
...wish you a very safe and pleasant evening.
晚安
Good night.
晚安哟
Gute Nacht.
小宝贝们也晚安哈
And you too, my babies.
谢谢你们甜蜜的眼皮吻
Oh, danke for the sweet eye kisses.
您先请  先生
After you, sir.
女士优先
Ladies first.
你先丢
I insist.
-我不会先扔掉  -我也不会先扔掉
- I'm not throwing mine out first. - I'm not throwing mine out first.
你跟全纽约一半的女孩都上过床
You've slept with half the women in New York.
我才是需要婚前协议保护的那个
I'm the one who needs a prenup.
你这些年骗走了我好几万大洋
You duped me out of thousands of dollars.
我才是需要婚前协议保护的那个
I'm the one who needs a prenup.
我刚想到还可以加上几条
I just thought of some more stuff to add.
我这还没完成一半呢
I'm not half finished.
我们开始吧
Let's dive in.
婚姻没那么复杂  不是吗
It should be simpler than this, shouldn't it?
是
Yeah.
或许不该这么复杂
Maybe it should be.
巴尼  你相信我吗
Barney, do you trust me?
不
No.
你相信我吗
Do you trust me?
不
No.
如果我们需要这么大费周章
If we really need something
才能够结婚的话
this complicated to get married...
没错
Yeah.
Damien Jurado  《Museunm Of Flight》
我担心被人发现*
*I was anxious to be found
你却永远可以回到*
*You can always go home
你安全的云中城堡*
*to the safety of your cloud.
我很遗憾  老兄
I'm sorry, buddy.
不过你还剩下老婆二号到八号
Hey, there's always wives two through eight.
从你的幻想中听来  她们蛮性感的
They sounded pretty hot in your fantasy.
除了老婆七号
All but wife seven.
我娶她纯粹因为她爸有钱
She was just there 'cause her dad was rich.
老实说  我没事
Actually, I'm okay.
我发现自己不可能找到  信任到可以结婚的那个人
I found out I'll never trust someone enough to get married,
那也没关系
and that's fine.
我的单身生活现在是  也永远将是
My single life is, and always will be,
传  等一下
legen... wait for it...
晚些时日
奇
...dary!
我的婚礼一定非常传奇
My wedding is gonna be legendary.
那么  婚前协议呢
So, prenup?
这次不用签了
Not this time.
亲爱的  可以去吃午饭了吗
Oh, hey you. Ready for lunch?
当然
Totally.
谢了
Thanks.
看到没  小拖船
See, Tugboat?
这就是爱  没错
That's love. Yeah.
路德维格准备给门把手打蜡了
You see, Ludwig has started to polish the doorknobs,
可维尔汉姆早就打过一次蜡了
but Wilhelm has already completed this task!
这虽然是喜剧
You know, it's big comedy.
但你会真心在乎其中的角色
but you really care about the characters.